// Gk Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the founder of Facebook?",
    answer: "Mark Zuckerberg",
    options: [
      "Mark Zuckerberg",
      "Bill Gates",
      "Larry Page",
      "Larry Ellison"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The following are all computing devices, except?",
    answer: "digital scanners",
    options: [
      "notebook computers",
      "digital scanners",
      "cellular telephones",
      "personal digital assistant"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who discovered sea route to India via Cape of Good Hope?",
    answer: "Vasco-da-Gama",
    options: [
      "Christopher Columbus",
      "Vasco-da-Gama",
      "Kepler",
      "Marco Polo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "CD-ROM stands for?",
    answer: "Compact Disk Read Only Memory",
    options: [
      "Compactable Disk Read Only",
      "Compact Disk Read Only Memory",
      "Compact Date Read Only Memory",
      "Compactable Read Only Memory"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which state of India records the highest production of tea?",
    answer: "Assam",
    options: [
      "Assam",
      "West Bengal",
      "Kerala",
      "Karnataka"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "Solve: 27% of 450 - ? % of 375 = 76.5",
  answer: "12",
  options: [
    "14",
    "12",
    "19",
    "15"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Complete the series - 1, 16, 81, 256, ?",
  answer: " 625",
  options: [
    "1296",
    " 625",
    "525",
    "446"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Select the related number: C : 27 :: F : ?",
  answer: " 216",
  options: [
    "64",
    "216",
    "36",
    "225"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Hirakud dam is on the river?",
  answer: "Mahanadi",
  options: [
    "Cauvery",
    "Mahanadi",
    "Krishna",
    "Sutlej"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is the numeric form of the number given here - One hundred three thousand, One hundred two?",
  answer: "103102",
  options: [
    "1003103",
    "103102",
    "103012",
    "13103"
  ]
},

];
